General
장군
General Shilang
석랑 장군
Everything in the city has been arranged
성안은 저희가 손 써놨습니다
There are agents in the city to assist
성안에 첩자가 있고
The northern garrison
성북 수비군은
Most are already dead drunk
대부분 술에 곯아떨어졌으니
Two warriors
이제 그 두 명이 성문만 열면
To welcome the general into the city
장군은 입성할 수 있습니다
Good dog
좋은 개로다
You'll be rewarded
상을 주마
Thank you, General
감사합니다 장군
Prepare the army
군을 정비하고
Ready for the assault
기습할 준비를 하거라
Yes
네
General
장군
Your subordinate
소인
For the general
장군을 위해서라면 죽음도 불사하겠습니다
But
다만
Could you release my
제 아내와 딸내미는
Wife and daughter first?
풀어주시면 안 될까요?
Of course
물론이지
I'll not only release them
풀어줄뿐더러
But also have a dozen Wuzhao warriors
오노 용사 십수 명을 붙여
Take good care of them
잘 접대해 주도록 하마
General, count me in
저도 끼워주세요
Count me in too
저도요
Good
좋아
Courageous
패기는 있구나
Shilang
석랑
You're a beast
이 짐승 같은 놈!
Xuan people
선나라인들은
A bunch of soft worms in the dirt
땅에 기어다니는 버러지들이지
Wuzhao warriors
오노의 용사들이여
Who dares to be the vanguard?
누가 선봉에 설 텐가?
I will
접니다
Good
좋아
I'll give you a unit
군사를 줄 테니
Break the city today
오늘 성을 함락하라
Yes
네
The gates are moving
성문이 열리고 있다
Brothers
형제들이여
Follow me in the charge
나를 따라 돌격한다
Gold, silver, and treasures
금은보화를
We'll take first
우리가 먼저 차지하자
Why are there people
병사들이 없는데
Something's not right
뭔가 이상해
We've been tricked
함정이다
Fire arrows
활을 쏴라
The enemy is trapped
적들은 독 안에 든 쥐다
Kill
죽여라
Report
보고드립니다
General
장군
The troops we just sent out
방금 보낸 부대가
Have been completely wiped out
전멸했습니다
What?
뭐라고!
Everyone, speak up
뭐라도 말해
What should we do?
이를 어찌하면 좋지
General
장군
Perhaps Prince of Jin
혹시 진왕이
Saw through our plan
우리 계책을 알고
And turned it against us
역이용한 건 아닐까요?
Do you think I'm blind?
난 뭐 눈이 먼 줄 알아!
Call them back
부대를 철수시켜
General, calm your anger
고정하세요, 장군
This plan
계책이 없는 건 아닙니다
As I know
소인이 알기로
The Wuyang commander Chen Ying
오양 수비 장수 진응은
Is backed by
배후가 선나라 영왕인데
Who doesn't get along with Prince of Jin
진왕과 사이가 안 좋아요
We can spread the false news that Prince of Jin
유실된 전국 옥새를
Got the seal
진왕이 손에 넣었다는 가짜 소문을
To Wuyang
오양에 퍼뜨리는 겁니다
You Xuan people
역시 선나라인끼리 잘 통하는구나
Do as he says
책사 말대로 해
Also
그리고
Have those who came line up
잡아 온 사람들을 줄 세워 놓거라
Yes
네